manaleak.com 2018-11-24

# Privacy Policy, Magic: The Gathering (MTG) & Miniature Wargames by Manaleak.com

**Manaleak.com Privacy Statement.**

Manaleak.com (Manaleak) is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This privacy statement explains Manaleak’s data collection and use practices with respect to its website (the Site). By using the pages in this site, you agree to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

**Collection of Personal Information.**

We may ask you for information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested. The personal information we collect may include your name, your address, contact information and other information about products and/or services requested through the Site.

Please note that we do not store credit card details.

The Site may also collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the Site. This information is used, among other things, to help improve the Site, analyze use trends and administer the Site.

**Use of Personal Information.**

Except as otherwise required by law, the personal information collected on this Site will be used solely to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) and/or product(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. In support of these purposes, Manaleak may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related Manaleak products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for your repeated entry of the same information. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with Manaleak, information collected by the Site may be combined with information collected in connection with other Manaleak products and services.

Manaleak occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as website hosting, mailing/shipping, etc.. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Manaleak may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Manaleak or the Site; or (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Manaleak and the Site.

**Control of Personal Information.**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, your personal information will not be shared outside of Manaleak and its subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.

If you register with the Site or purchase products through the Site, you will need to choose a user name and password. By using the user name and password, you will be able to access certain portions of the Site that are unavailable to unregistered users and will be able to purchase new products without re-entering your personal information and credit card number. You are solely responsible for choosing the user name and password and maintaining the confidentiality of the password that you choose. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Failure to protect the security of these items may permit unauthorized individuals to obtain your personal information and your credit card information. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Security of Personal Information.**

Manaleak is strongly committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

**Credit Card Transactions.**

Some features of the Manaleak site enable credit card transactions via Paypal and NoChex. Manaleak assures you that we have taken measures to make such transactions secure for our members.

Paypal and NoChex utilize industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) servers to encrypt your information and prevent unauthorized access.

Shortly after an order is processed, you will receive a confirmation via e-mail. You are advised to print out and save a copy of the order confirmation for verification necessary to resolve any issues with your order.

We guarantee that every transaction will be 100 percent safe. This means you are not responsible for unauthorized transactions posted to your credit card that occur as a result of submitting a credit card number to Paypal or NoChex. Paypal and NoChex uses industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) servers on our transaction pages. SSL encrypts all of your personal information including name, address, and credit card number to prevent unauthorized access as the information travels over the Internet.

**Cookies.**

We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server and that helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

The use of cookies simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and provides other similar benefits to users of the Site. When you return to the Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Site’s features. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site.

**Links to Other Sites.**

This site contains links to other sites. Manaleak is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Changes to this Statement.**

We reserve the right to update this privacy statement from time to time. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement, as amended from time to time.

**Contact Information.**

Manaleak welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that Manaleak has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us electronically or via postal mail at the following address, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem:

**Manaleak.com (Inside Lifestyle Express)**

**32 Broad Street**

**Worcester**

**WR1 3NH**

**England**

E. [Info@Manaleak.com](http://www.manaleak.com/store/contact_us.php)

T. 01905 745 032

W. [Manaleak.com](http://www.manaleak.com/)

### Please let us know what you think below...
